Finding Aid for the Lou Derman Papers PASC.0099
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television writings
  - ALL IN THE FAMILY
    - EDITH'S FRIEND,., 2/5/1975; Final draft (Box 14)
    - EVERYBODY DOES IT,., 1/15/1975; Final draft (Box 14)
    - GEORGE AND ARCHIE MAKE A DEAL,., 11/6/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - GLORIA'S SHOCK,., 10/8/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - JEFFERSONS MOVE UP, THE,., 10/24/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - LIONEL THE LIVE-IN,., 9/25/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - MIKE MAKES HIS MOVE,., 2/19/1975; Final draft (Box 14)
    - MIKE'S FRIEND,., 9/11/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - NO SMOKING,., 2/12/1975; Final draft (Box 14)
    - PRISONER IN THE HOUSE,., 12/5/1974; Final draft (Box 14)
    - WE KNOW WHERE ARCHIE IS,., 9/13/1974; Second draft (Box 14)
  - CHICAGO TEDDY BEARS, THE
    - BIG FREEZE, THE,., ca. 1973; [Pilot?] (Box 7)
  - DECEMBER BRIDE
    - ACCIDENT, THE,., (No date) (Box 7)
    - CHICKEN SALAD,., (No date) (Box 7)
    - CHINESE DINNER, THE,., (No date) (Box 7)
    - GRUNION HUNTING,., 9/2/1954; Revised (Box 7)
    - LILY HIRES A MAID,., (No date) (Box 7)
    - LILY'S MOTHER-IN-LAW,., 9/2/1954; Revised (Box 7)
    - MY SOLDIER,., (No date) (Box 7)
    - VETERINARIAN, THE,., (No date) (Box 7)
    - BREAKUP, THE (TRILOGY),., 1/22/1955; Filming date (Box 8)
    - CHRISTMAS SHOW,., 12/20/1954; Release date (Box 8)
    - GIGOLO, THE,., (No date) (Box 8)
    - GRANDFATHER CLOCK, THE,., 11/26/1954; Revised (Box 8)
    - INSURANCE SHOW,., 12/18/1954; Filming date (Box 8)
    - JEALOUSY,., 12/30/1954; Original film date (Box 8)
    - LILY WANTS TO PAY HER WAY,., 11/11/1964; Revised (Box 8)
    - LILY, THE ARTIST,., (No date) (Box 8)
    - LILY'S NIECE,., 2/5/1955; Filming date (Box 8)
    - LUAU, THE,., (No date) (Box 8)
    - MATT COOKS,., 2/19/1955 (Box 8)
    - MEXICO,., 1/25/1955; Revised (Box 8)
    - RICH MAN,., 10/25/1954; Revised (Box 8)
    - SENTIMENTALIST, THE,., 12/18/1954; Filming date (Box 8)
    - SURPRISE PARTY,., 12/30/1954; Original film date (Box 8)
    - URANIUM SHOW,., (No date); Revised (Box 8)
    - WEDDING PREPARATIONS,., 1/15/1955; Filming date (Box 8)
    - BIG GAME HUNTER,., 10/13/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - BOXING SHOW, THE,., 8/5/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - GOSSIP,., 3/19/1955; Filming date (Box 9)
    - GUEST STAR SHOW, THE,., (No date) (Box 9)
    - LET YOURSELF GO,., (No date) (Box 9)
    - LILY AND THE WOLF,., (No date) (Box 9)
    - LILY IS BORED,., (No date) (Box 9)
    - LILY'S SONG,., 4/1/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - LINEUP, THE,., 4/2/1955; Filming date (Box 9)
    - MATT'S MUSTACHE,., 3/23/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - OTHER COUPLE, THE,., 4/9/1955; Filming date (Box 9)
    - PIZZA SHOW, THE,., 8/1/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - PSYCHIATRIST,., 3/12/1955; Filming date (Box 9)
    - RUTH NEGLECTS MATT,., 9/13/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - SHOPLIFTER SHOW, THE,., (No date) (Box 9)
    - SKIDROW,., 10/11/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - THEATER TICKETS,., 2/18/1955; Revised (Box 9)
    - CHRISTMAS SHOW,., 12/20/1954; Release date (Box 10)
    - FAMILY QUARREL,., 11/2/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - HANDCUFFS,., 2/8/1956; Revised (Box 10)
    - HIGH SIERRAS,., 11/8/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - MATT'S MOVIE CAREER,., 12/7/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - MATT'S MUSTACHE,., 3/26/1955; Filming date (Box 10)
    - OPERATION COLE SLAW,., (No date) (Box 10)
    - RATE YOUR MATE,., 11/17/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - RUDY VALEE SHOW,., 12/13/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - RUTH GETS A JOB,., 2/4/1956; Filming date (Box 10)
    - SUNKEN DEN,., 12/16/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - TEXAS #3 (THE BREAKUP),., 1/10/1956; Revised (Box 10)
    - TEXAS SHOW #1,., (No date) (Box 10)
    - TEXAS SHOW #2,., 12/21/1955; Revised (Box 10)
    - TRAILER SHOW,., (No date) (Box 10)
    - WRESTLER, THE,., 1/21/1956; Filming date (Box 10)
    - AIRPLANE SHOW,., 10/8/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - ANTIQUE SHOW,., (No date) (Box 11)
    - ARMY BUDDY,., 12/10/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - BABY REHEARSAL,., 12/3/1957; Revised, filming date (Box 11)
    - BOUNCER SHOW,., 1/7/1958; Filming date (Box 11)
    - BUTLER SHOW,., 10/1/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - CONTOUR CHAIR,., 11/26/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - ED WYNN SHOW,., 1/28/1958; Revised, filming date (Box 11)
    - FRED MAC MURRAY SHOW,., 1/21/1958; Filming date (Box 11)
    - GOLF LESSON, THE,., 8/20/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - HOT MEAL,., (No date) (Box 11)
    - HOUSEMOTHER,., 11/12/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - MATT'S GRAY HAIR,., 9/24/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - MEAN GRANDFATHER,., 8/13/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - MICROPHONE SHOW,., 9/17/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - MUSCLEMAN SHOW,., 11/19/1957; Revised, filming date (Box 11)
    - OTHER WOMAN, THE,., 9/7/1957; Revised (Box 11)
    - PARROT SHOW, THE,., (No date) (Box 11)
    - PHOTOGRAPHY SHOW,., 7/30/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - RUTH GOES HOME TO MOTHER,., 7/23/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - SLEEP TEACHING,., (No date); Revised (Box 11)
    - SPORTS CAR,., 8/27/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - VALLEE'S PROTOGE,., 8/6/1957; Filming date (Box 11)
    - ALASKA SHOW,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 12)
    - AUNT EMILY,., 2/11/1958; Revised, filming date (Box 12)
    - BEATNIK SHOW,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - BRIDE'S FATHER-IN-LAW,., 7/29/1958; Filming date (Box 12)
    - CAPISTRANO SHOW,., 2/18/1958; Filming date; draft 1 (Box 12)
    - CAR FOR CHRISTMAS,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 12)
    - CHILD OF NATURE,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - CHIMP SHOW,., 8/12/1958; Filming date (Box 12)
    - EDGAR BERGEN SHOW,., 8/19/1958; Filming date; draft 1 (Box 12)
    - FENWICK ARMS,., 8/26/1958; Filming date (Box 12)
    - GILBERT ROLAND SHOW,., 2/25/1958; Filming date (Box 12)
    - HILDA'S ENGAGEMENT,., 9/9/1958; Filming date; draft 1 (Box 12)
    - HORSE PHOBIA,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - LILY ON BOAT,., 3/11/1958; Revised, filming date (Box 12)
    - LILY'S BIRTHDAY DRESS,., 12/11/1957; Revised (Box 12)
    - MATT-PETE FIGHT (WAS:MATT JOINS A LODGE),., 3/4/1958; Revised, filming date (Box 12)
    - MICKEY ROONEY SHOW,., 3/18/1958; Revised, filming date (Box 12)
    - NURSE SHOW,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - POST OFFICE SHOW,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - POWER TOOL,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - TOUGH MOTHER-IN-LAW,., (No date) (Box 12)
    - WEDDING FLOAT,., 1/14/1958; Filming date; draft 1 (Box 12)
    - ZSA ZSA SHOW,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 12)
    - BALD BABY,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - HI FI SHOW,., 1/13/1959; Filming date (Box 13)
    - LILY BABYSITS,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - LILY GOES FISHING,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - LILY HELPS TWILLY,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - LILY, THE EXAMPLE,., 3/24/1959; Filming date (Box 13)
    - LILY'S ADVICE COLUMN,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - LILY'S BLIND DATE,., 12/16/1958; Revised, filming date (Box 13)
    - LINDA ON TV,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - MARTIAN SHOW, THE,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - NURSE IS FIRED,., 12/9/1958; Filming date (Box 13)
    - PETE HAS BABY,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - RORY CALHOUN STORY,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - RUTH THE BRAIN,., 2/10/1959; Filming date (Box 13)
    - SCOTCH SHOW, THE,., 1/20/1959; Filming date (Box 13)
    - STAN LOSES HIS NERVE,., (No date); draft 1 (Box 13)
    - BUDGET SHOW,., 11/27/1956; Filming date (Box 18)
    - CHICKEN FARM SHOW,., 11/13/1956; Filming date (Box 18)
    - FOOTBALL HERO,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - HOMECOMING SHOW,., 11/20/1956; Filming date (Box 18)
    - HOUSE ON BLOCKS,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - INDIAN SHOW,., 12/3/1956; Release date (Box 18)
    - JOCKEY, THE,., 9/14/1956; Revised (Box 18)
    - MAN TOWN SHOW,., 11/6/1956; Filming date (Box 18)
    - MARJORIE MAIN SHOW,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - NEW YEAR'S PARTY SHOW,., 10/9/1956; Filming date (Box 18)
    - PRIZE FIGHTER, THE,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - PROWLER SHOW, THE,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - REDECORATING,., 8/22/1956; Revised (Box 18)
    - RITZY NEIGHBORHOOD,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - RORY CALHOUN SHOW,., (No date) (Box 18)
    - ROYALTY SHOW,., 10/16/1956; Filming date (Box 18)
    - DO IT YOURSELF,., 2/19/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - DUCK HUNTING,., 1/8/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - ENGAGEMENT SHOW,., 1/15/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - ENGLISHMAN, THE,., 2/19/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - HOBO SHOW, THE,., 1/29/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - KISSING BOOTH,., 2/5/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - LILY-HILDA FIGHT,., 3/19/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - MASQUERADE PARTY,., 1/22/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - MOTHER-IN-LAW CLUB,., (No date) (Box 19)
    - MOUNTAIN CLIMBING,., 3/12/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - OLD MAN, THE,., 2/26/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - PIANO SHOW,., 12/18/1956; Filming date (Box 19)
    - SONG PLUGGING,., 3/5/1957; Filming date (Box 19)
    - STUDY GROUP,., 12/4/1956; Filming date (Box 19)
    - BEAUTY PAGEANT,., 3/20/1956; Filming date (Box 20)
    - JAYWALKER,., Date: 1954 Oct.; no number; with cast list (Box 20)
    - LILY AND THE SAILOR,., 3/27/1956; Filming date (Box 20)
    - LILY IN A GAS STATION,., 1/24/1956; Revised (Box 20)
    - LILY, THE MATCHMAKER,., 4/3/1956; Filming date (Box 20)
    - PETE'S BROTHER-IN-LAW,., 2/21/1956; Filming date (Box 20)
    - RUTH'S HAIRCUT,., Date: 1954 Oct.; no number; with cast list (Box 20)
    - SWIMMING POOL,., 4/10/1956; Filming date (Box 20)
  - GALE STORM SHOW, THE (OH! SUSANNA)
    - AFRICAN DRUMS,., 11/10/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - BIRTHDAY FOR GINO,., 11/27/1959 (Box 16)
    - CAPTAIN COURAGEOUS,., 12/28/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - CAPTAIN DADDY,., 11/3/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - FAMILY REUNION,., 10/12/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - GOODBYE, DOCTOR,., 10/5/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - IT'S MAGIC,., 1/26/1950; Revised (Box 16)
    - LOVE, BY YIMINY!,., 11/23/1959 (Box 16)
    - MADE IN HONG KONG,., 1/4/1960 (Box 16)
    - MOTHER STEPS OUT,., 12/14/1959 (Box 16)
    - NO TEARS FOR THE CAPTAIN,., 11/9/1959 (Box 16)
    - NUGEY, COME HOME,., 9/16/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - ONE COIN IN THE FOUNTAIN,., 1/12/1960; Revised (Box 16)
    - S.O.S DAD,., 12/16/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - SHOW BIZ,., 1/12/1960 (Box 16)
    - SPANISH SOUVENIR,., (No date) (Box 16)
    - SWEDISH STEWARD, THE,., 9/25/1959 (Box 16)
    - TRIP FOR AUNTIE, A,., 11/30/1959; Revised (Box 16)
    - WEDDING AT SEA,., 10/18/1959; Revised (Box 16)
  - GIRL WITH SOMETHING EXTRA, THE
    - GUESS WHO'S FEEDING THE PIGEONS,., 11/2/1973 (Box 7)
    - IRRECONCILABLE SAMENESS,., 12/27/1973 (Box 7)
  - GOOD GUYS, THE
    - BUTTONS AND BEAUS,., 8/12/1969 (Box 15)
    - SEALED WITH A KISS,., 6/17/1969 (Box 15)
  - GOOD TIMES
    - GOD'S BUSINESS IS GOOD BUSINESS,., 1/25/1974 (Box 15)
    - JUNIOR AND SENIOR,., 3/6/1974 (Box 15)
    - MY SON THE LOVER,., 4/16/1974 (Box 15)
    - TV COMMERCIAL, THE,., 4/3/1974 (Box 15)
  - HERE'S LUCY
    - GETTING LUCY'S GOAT,., 3/18/1971; No number (Box 14)
    - LUCY AND THE ASTRONAUTS,., 5/6/1971; No number (Box 14)
    - LUCY IN THE JUNGLE,., 7/27/1971; No number (Box 14)
    - LUCY THE MOUNTAIN CLIMBER,., 3/22/1971; No number (Box 14)
    - LUCY THE SKYDIVER,., 1/20/1970; No number (Box 14)
    - LUCY, PART-TIME WIFE,., 7/23/1970; No number (Box 14)
    - LUCY, PART-TIME WIFE,., 8/12/1970; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY AND CAROL BURNETT,., 12/3/1969; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY AND CAROL BURNETT,., 10/22/1969; Final draft (Box 15)
    - LUCY AND MA PARKER,., 4/27/1970; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY AND MA PARKER,., 4/27/1970; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY AND THE GUITAR,., 5/22/1970; Final draft (Box 15)
    - LUCY AND THE GUITAR,., 5/22/1970; Final draft (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE AMERICAN MOTHER,., 3/3/1970; Final draft (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE AMERICAN MOTHER,., 5/13/1970; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE LAUNDRESS,., 9/16/1969; Final draft (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE LAUNDRESS,., 9/2/1969; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE SKYDIVER,., 1/20/1970; No number (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE TAXI DANCER,., 2/4/1970; Not filmed - numbered (Box 15)
    - LUCY THE TAXI DANCER,., 2/5/1970; Final draft (Box 15)
  - HOW TO MARRY A MILLIONAIRE
    - LOCO AND THE GAMBLER,., 5/16/1958; Final draft (Box 20)
    - LOCO LEAVES HOME,., 1/21/1958; Final draft (Box 20)
  - LOVE THY NEIGHBOR
    - RED IS BEAUTIFUL,., ca. 1973; [Pilot?] (Box 7)
  - MILTON BERLE SHOW, THE
    - WITH GUESTS LUCILLE BALL & DESI ARNAZ,., 9/14/1959; Revised (Box 20)
  - MISTER ED
    - AUNT, THE,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - BUSY WIFE,., 11/28/1960; Revised (Box 1)
    - ED AGREES TO TALK,., 3/13/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - ED THE LOVER,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - ED THE SONGWRITER,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - ED THE STOOLPIGEON,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - ED THE TOUT,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - ED THE WITNESS,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - ED'S MOTHER,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - ED'S NEW SHOES,., 3/17/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - FIRST MEETING, THE,., 11/10/1960; Revised (Box 1)
    - KIDDY PARK,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - LITTLE BOY,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - MAN FOR VELMA, A,., 3/6/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - MISSING STATUE,., 1/19/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - MUSTACHE, THE,., 3/24/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - PAGEANT, THE,., 1/9/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - PSYCHOANALYST SHOW,., (No date) (Box 1)
    - SORORITY HOUSE,., 1/17/1961; Revised (Box 1)
    - STABLE FOR THREE,., 11/30/1960; Revised (Box 1)
    - VENTRILOQUIST, THE,., 11/21/1960; Revised (Box 1)
    - CONTEST, THE,., 3/29/1961 (Box 2)
    - ED AND THE ELEPHANT,., 10/20/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED CRIES WOLF,., 4/20/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE BENEFICIARY,., 10/16/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE HERO,., 10/16/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE HORSE DOCTOR,., 12/29/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE HUNTER,., 9/20/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE JUMPER,., 6/29/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE REDECORATOR,., 8/4/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE SALESMAN,., 10/4/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED THE VOTER,., 9/5/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED'S ANCESTORS,., 7/28/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED'S BED,., 10/30/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - ED'S WORD OF HONOR,., (No date) (Box 2)
    - HORSETRONAUT, THE,., 7/26/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - MISTER ED'S BLUES,., 9/26/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - MY SON, MY SON,., 7/26/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - OTHER WOMAN, THE,., 3/23/1961 (Box 2)
    - PINE LAKE LODGE,., 4/27/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - WILBUR SELLS ED,., 4/3/1961 (Box 2)
    - ZSA ZSA,., 9/29/1961; Revised (Box 2)
    - BALD HORSE,., 1/9/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - BICYCLE SHOW,., 10/23/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - CLINT EASTWOOD SHOW,., (No date) (Box 3)
    - DISAPPEARING HORSE,., 10/18/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - DOCTOR ED,., 1/14/1963; Revised (Box 3)
    - ED FINALLY TALKS,., 5/8/1961; Revised (Box 3)
    - ED THE BEACHCOMBER,., 1/22/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - ED THE EMANCIPATOR,., (No date) (Box 3)
    - ED THE PILGRIM,., 11/5/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - ED THE ZEBRA,., 1/25/1963; Revised (Box 3)
    - ED'S NEW NEIGHBORS,., 12/28/1961; Revised (Box 3)
    - HORSE OF A DIFFERENT COLOR,., 10/31/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - HORSE PARTY,., 10/10/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - HORSE TALK,., 12/14/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - HORSE WASH,., 11/28/1961; Revised (Box 3)
    - NO HORSES ALLOWED,., 1/11/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - OLE ROCKIN' CHAIR,., (No date) (Box 3)
    - PRICE OF APPLES, THE,., (No date) (Box 3)
    - SNOW VALLEY,., (No date) (Box 3)
    - UNEMPLOYMENT SHOW,., (No date) (Box 3)
    - WORKING WIVES,., 12/14/1962; Revised (Box 3)
    - WRESTLER, THE,., 11/1/1961; Revised (Box 3)
    - BE KIND TO HUMANS,., 8/23/1963 (Box 4)
    - DON'T LAUGH AT HORSES,., 8/2/1963 (Box 4)
    - ED DISCOVERS AMERICA,., 8/26/1963 (Box 4)
    - ED GETS THE MUMPS,., 9/17/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED IN THE PEACE CORPS,., 10/17/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED THE CHAUFFEUR,., 10/16/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED THE DESERT RAT,., 10/10/1963 (Box 4)
    - ED THE DONKEY,., 1/6/1964; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED THE MUSICIAN,., 9/18/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED THE SHISHKEBOB,., 10/8/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED VISITS A GYPSY,., 12/4/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ED'S CHRISTMAS STORY,., 11/13/1963 (Box 4)
    - ED'S DENTIST,., 11/5/1963 (Box 4)
    - GETTING ED'S GOAT,., 9/17/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - HOME SWEET TRAILER,., 10/4/1963 (Box 4)
    - LEO DUROCHER MEETS MR. ED,., 7/31/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - LOVE THY NEIGHBOR,., 10/17/1963 (Box 4)
    - MAE WEST MEETS ED,., 1/10/1964; Revised (Box 4)
    - OH THOSE HATS!,., 9/19/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - OLD SWAYBACK,., 12/17/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - PATTER OF LITTLE HOOVES,., 8/7/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - PAYROLL SAVINGS FILM,., 9/24/1963 (Box 4)
    - PROWLER, THE,., 1/10/1964 (Box 4)
    - SADDLES AND GOWNS,., 1/20/1964; Revised (Box 4)
    - TALLER THAN SHE,., 8/23/1963 (Box 4)
    - WILBUR POST, HONORARY HORSE,., 8/5/1963; Revised (Box 4)
    - ANIMAL JURY,., 9/21/1964 (Box 5)
    - DRAGON HORSE, THE,., 11/18/1964 (Box 5)
    - ED THE PILOT,., 10/14/1964; Revised (Box 5)
    - ED THE POOL PLAYER,., 8/5/1964; Revised (Box 5)
    - ED THE RACE HORSE,., 7/13/1964 (Box 5)
    - ED THE SENTRY,., 7/24/1964 (Box 5)
    - ED THE STOWAWAY,., 10/22/1964; Revised (Box 5)
    - ED'S BACHELOR APARTMENT,., 6/24/1964 (Box 5)
    - ED'S COLD TAIL,., 2/17/1965; Revised (Box 5)
    - ED'S JUICE STAND,., 10/27/1964 (Box 5)
    - HEAVY RIDER, THE,., 9/30/1964 (Box 5)
    - HI-FI HORSES,., 8/27/1964; Revised (Box 5)
    - JOHNNY PROVOST MEETS ED,., 9/16/1964; Revised (Box 5)
    - LIKE FATHER, LIKE HORSE,., 5/19/1964 (Box 5)
    - MAE GOES WEST,., 7/8/1964 (Box 5)
    - MY HORSE, THE SCOUT,., 8/14/1964 (Box 5)
    - TUNNEL TO FREEDOM,., 5/21/1964 (Box 5)
    - WHAT KIND OF FOAL AM I?,., 12/3/1964; Revised (Box 5)
    - ANYBODY GOT A ZEBRA?,., 9/7/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - BANK ROBBERY, THE,., 2/18/1965 (Box 6)
    - CHEROKEE ED,., 10/28/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - COLDFINGER,., 8/20/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - DON'T SKIN THAT BEAR,., 9/22/1965 (Box 6)
    - ED A GO-GO,., 7/22/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - ED BREAKS THE HIP CODE,., 8/10/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - ED MEETS EDITH HEAD,., (No date); not filmed (Box 6)
    - ED THE ARTIST,., 4/5/1965 (Box 6)
    - ED THE BRIDEGROOM,., 9/27/1965 (Box 6)
    - ED THE COUNTERSPY,., 7/23/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - ED THE GODFATHER,., 2/1/1965 (Box 6)
    - ED'S CONTACT LENSES,., 2/9/1965 (Box 6)
    - ED'S DICTION TEACHER,., 12/17/1964 (Box 6)
    - HORSE AND THE PUSSYCAT, THE,., 9/23/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - JOHNNY LONGDEN RIDES ED,., (No date); not filmed (Box 6)
    - LOVE AND THE SINGLE HORSE,., 8/5/1965 (Box 6)
    - MISTER ED GOES TO COLLEGE,., 10/28/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - MY HORSE HATES MOTORCYCLES,., 10/18/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - MY HORSE THE MAILMAN,., 3/5/1965 (Box 6)
    - NEVER RIDE HORSES!,., 1/19/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - ROBIN HOOD ED,., 3/26/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - TV OR NOT TV,., 9/13/1965; Revised (Box 6)
    - WHISKERS AND TAILS,., 3/19/1965; Revised (Box 6)
  - NEW TEMPERATURES RISING SHOW, THE
    - IS THERE A LADY DOCTOR IN THE HOUSE?,., 12/6/1973 (Box 7)
    - KID GENIUS,., 1/2/1974; No number (Box 7)
  - PHYLLIS DILLER SHOW, THE
    - GODDESS OF LOVE,., 1/24/1967 (Box 17)
    - HOUSE IS NOT A ZOO, A,., 1/3/1967; Revised (Box 17)
    - KRUMP, THE PLAYBOY,., 2/4/1967 (Box 17)
    - MARRY A MILLION,., 1/19/1967 (Box 17)
    - NOBODY HERE BUT US CHICKENS,., 1/13/1967 (Box 17)
    - PORTRAIT OF KRUMP,., 1/6/1967 (Box 17)
  - PRUITTS OF SOUTHAMPTON, THE
    - GHOST OF PRUITT MANSION, THE,., 12/9/1966 (Box 17)
    - HOW TO BE A MILLIONAIRE,., 11/29/1966 (Box 17)
    - HOW TO ROB A MILLIONAIRE,., 10/25/1966; Revised (Box 17)
    - HUBCAP CAPER, THE,., 11/10/1966 (Box 17)
    - LITTLE MISS FIXIT,., 11/21/1966 (Box 17)
    - MY BROTHER HARVEY,., 11/18/1966; Revised (Box 17)
    - PHYLLIS, QUEEN OF THE ROAD,., 10/20/1966 (Box 17)
    - PHYLLIS, THE BEAUTY QUEEN,., 12/5/1966 (Box 17)
    - PHYLLIS--THE BATGIRL,., 10/17/1966; Revised (Box 17)
    - PHYLLIS--THE STAR,., 10/18/1966; Revised (Box 17)
    - SANTA WAS A LADY,., 11/2/1966 (Box 17)
  - RAY MILLAND SHOW, THE
    - DOLL'S HOUSE, THE,., Date: 1954 Oct.; no number; with cast list (Box 20)
  - SPRING BYINGTON SHOW, THE
    - PILOT,., 8/5/1959; Final draft (Box 20)
  - TUGBOAT ANNIE
    - PILOT,., 1/23/1956 (Box 20)